[{"answer": "So, where does your family come from", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Well, my dads side of the family is from Indiana and my moms side of th", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 12, "question": "So, where does your family come from", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " So do you see your extended family a lot then", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Well, my dads side of the family is from Indiana and my moms side of th", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Not really.  My family is pretty small and I dont have a lot of living relatives lef", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": " So do you see your extended family a lot then", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " I guess it is kind of far to travel to those states frequently.  Do you have a lot o", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Not really.  My family is pretty small and I dont have a lot of living relatives lef", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " No, actually, Im an only-child", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I guess it is kind of far to travel to those states frequently.  Do you have a lot o", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Your family is pretty small then.  So, its just you, your mom, and your da", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 27, "question": " No, actually, Im an only-child", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Well, my parents are divorced and my dad moved back to Indiana a few year", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Your family is pretty small then.  So, its just you, your mom, and your da", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Oh.  Im sorry to hear that", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Well, my parents are divorced and my dad moved back to Indiana a few year", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Thats OK.  My parents fought a lot when they were together, so its better tha", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh.  Im sorry to hear that", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " You and your mom must be close then", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Thats OK.  My parents fought a lot when they were together, so its better tha", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " We are.  I miss her a lot now that Im at school.  I have a picture of us.  Want t", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 44, "question": " You and your mom must be close then", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 50, "question": " We are.  I miss her a lot now that Im at school.  I have a picture of us.  Want t", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Thats my mom and me on vacation last year", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " You really take after your mom!  You look like sisters", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Thats my mom and me on vacation last year", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " I know.  Everyone says we look alike.  What about you?  Do you have a bi", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " You really take after your mom!  You look like sisters", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Yeah.  I have a really big family.  They all live in Florida, so I have six aunts, fiv", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I know.  Everyone says we look alike.  What about you?  Do you have a bi", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " That sounds like a lot", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Yeah.  I have a really big family.  They all live in Florida, so I have six aunts, fiv", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " It is.  Plus, I have seven siblings.  Two sisters and five brothers", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " That sounds like a lot", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Your parents had eight children!  Thats so many", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " It is.  Plus, I have seven siblings.  Two sisters and five brothers", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I know.  Our house is crazy.  Im the oldest and I always had to baby-sit", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Your parents had eight children!  Thats so many", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " How old are your siblings", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": " I know.  Our house is crazy.  Im the oldest and I always had to baby-sit", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Lets see Theyre 20, 18, 14, 10, 8, 4, and 1 and a half", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 64, "question": " How old are your siblings", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Whoa!  Thats a pretty big age range", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Lets see Theyre 20, 18, 14, 10, 8, 4, and 1 and a half", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I know its unusual.  My parents just love having kids, I guess", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Whoa!  Thats a pretty big age range", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " So, do you see your family often", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 67, "question": " I know its unusual.  My parents just love having kids, I guess", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Yeah.  They live about 10 minutes from my apartment.  I see them almost ever", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " So, do you see your family often", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " That must be so nice to have such a big family close by", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Yeah.  They live about 10 minutes from my apartment.  I see them almost ever", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " It is.  It can be a little hectic sometimes, but its nice to know that there are so man", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 76, "question": " That must be so nice to have such a big family close by", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": "Thats so different from what Im used to", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 80, "question": " It is.  It can be a little hectic sometimes, but its nice to know that there are so man", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " You should come over for dinner at our house one Sunday.  They love to meet m", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Thats so different from what Im used to", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Sure.  Thatd be fun", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 85, "question": " You should come over for dinner at our house one Sunday.  They love to meet m", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " OK.  Let me tell my mom and Ill ask her what date will be good and let you know", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Sure.  Thatd be fun", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Sounds good", "docId": "07-10", "aSentId": 87, "question": " OK.  Let me tell my mom and Ill ask her what date will be good and let you know", "qSentId": 86}]
